You know, Sir, I feel that...
even if we caught Berdugo,
his viciousness is still around.
That's him!
That's the real Berdugo.
He's Andrew's family.
- That's his brother-in-law.
- No.
We need solid evidence
if we don't want Berdugo
to escape.
Andrew? I didn't expect
to see you here.
I came here to check on you,
Tomas.
Of course, after Berdugo
was caught, right?
That's very thoughtful of you,
Andrew...
but I'm fine.
Is there something
you're not telling me?
Let's just wait for Andrew.
What does Andrew
have to do with this?
He's getting evidence.
What evidence?
Do you still remember
the teddy bear...
you would always show me?
Is it still here?
[OBB]
He still hasn't answered.
[HEAVY MUSIC PLAYING]
“Blood is thicker than water?”
What do you mean?
Berdugo is Andrew's relative?
Jin Ho, he still has
a few minutes.
He hasn't broken the deal yet.
He'll come here soon.
[HEAVY MUSIC CONTINUES]
Andrew...
You didn't run away.
I would never do that.
I'm always on the side
of truth...
even if my enemy is family.
Major...
this is what we need.
Because Tomas Limjoco...
is the real Berdugo.
[HEAVY MUSIC CONTINUES]
[VIDEO GAME SFX]
[KNOCK ON THE DOOR]
Oh, Dad.
[UNEASY MUSIC PLAYING]
Why aren't you asleep yet?
Mom said I still have
an hour to play
after my homework.
Did your Uncle Andrew
drop by earlier?
What did he want?
I forgot, Uncle.
I haven't even watched
the video yet.
It's okay. I'll check it first.
But promise me
this stays between us.
Don't tell your mom and dad.
Why?
Because I have a surprise
for them.
[CHUCKLES PRETENTIOUSLY]
Okay, Uncle. Sure.
He just said good night, Dad.
Are you sure?
Yes, Dad.
All right.
Wrap it up, okay?
Don't stay up late.
Yes.
- Good night.
- Good night, Dad.
[UNEASY MUSIC CONTINUES]
The lies must end tonight!
Tell your family
who you really are,
that you're the leader
of a syndicate...
and you are Berdugo!
[INQUISITIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
You think they'll believe you?
I'm telling my children now!
[INQUISITIVE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[REBECCA GRUNTING]
[THUDS]
[REBECCA GROANING]
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
He's a monster!
[STIRRING MUSIC CONTINUES]
Mom knows what happened
with Tomas.
[STIRRING MUSIC CONTINUES]
Andrew...
I know this is very hard
for you,
but as an investigator,
I just want to understand...
what role your mother had
with Berdugo.
But before that,
we need to capture Berdugo.
Especially now.
It's dangerous...
Sir Tomas still controls
the situation,
especially at the rest house
where your mom is.
Isn't he controlling
the people taking care
of your Mommy Rebecca?
I won't let that happen
to my family.
I need to keep them safe!
But how?
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
I have an idea...
but, I'll need help with this.
At last, Tirada enjoyers.
We've tracked down the notorious
drug supplier, Berdugo.
[GALVANIZING MUSIC PLAYING]
Despite hiding behind
a legitimate business,
the truth has come out, Tirada.
Matias is indeed the head
of that illegal operation.
We witnessed the dangers
faced by the police.
And now, we can say it's over.
This chaos is over,
and Berdugo is behind bars.
So, congratulations
to Bolagos Police
for a job well done
and to all agencies involved,
especially Major Miguel Delgado
and Unit 2.
Until next time,
Tirada listeners.
Cut.
Andrew...
when did you become a parrot?
That's the same report
everyone else gave.
[INQUISITIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
The numbers are low.
What?
The number of viewers is low
during our live,
and as it went on,
engagement kept dropping.
Really?
I'm more surprised
anyone stayed.
Well, how could they?
It was basic.
Lacking insight.
Exactly, here,
I'll read the comments.
This one says...
“The report was boring,
so watching was boring too.”
Here's another...
“Your Boss Idol is tired.”
Ouch.
With a crying emoji.
Another one...
“He's ran out of guts already?”
Just chill.
It's all part of the plan.
What plan?
[INQUISITIVE MUSIC CONTINUES]
The truth has come out,
Tirada enjoyers.
Matias is indeed the head
of that illegal operation.
[PHONE RINGS]
[UNEASY MUSIC PLAYING]
Yes?
Berdugo, it's quiet here
at the precinct.
No one's moving
among Delgado's men.
Matias's arraignment
is proceeding.
He'll be transferred
to the provincial jail.
Looks like you have nothing
to worry about, Berdugo.
Okay, just stay alert.
Always, Boss.
[UNEASY MUSIC CONTINUES]
We'll see grandmother again!
Yay!
Just be a good girl, okay?
Yes, Mommy.
[CHUCKLES]
- You too.
- Yes.
What's going on?
We're going to the rest house
to visit mommy.
She's getting better,
but if the kids visit her,
it could help her more.
But we'll be back tonight.
I'll go with you guys.
[FOREBODING MUSIC PLAYING]
You're coming?
Yes, I want to be with you.
Daddy's coming too?
Yay!
Okay, let's go.
[FOREBODING MUSIC CONTINUES]
[PHONE CHIMES]
[UNEASY MUSIC PLAYING]
[UNEASY MUSIC CONTINUES]
Are you okay?
Tomas went with Yvette.
Oh, no!
He knows.
Maybe he just wants family time.
[UNEASY MUSIC CONTINUES]
Major, this is Andrew.
There's been a change.
Tomas went with Yvette
to the rest house.
Copy!
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Andrew...
tell Yvette to go straight
to the rest house.
After that, we'll handle it.
All units, change of plan!
We're heading straight
to the rest house.
Secure the Dizons.
I'll take care of Berdugo.
Loud and clear, Sir.
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Major, what I feared
has already happened.
My family is in danger now
because Tomas went with them.
Major, this wasn't our plan.
I know, Andrew, it's hard
to control the situation.
But let's plan it carefully.
Just trust us.
We can't move...
until we're sure
your family is safe.
We know what Tomas can do...
even to the people close to him.
That's why we need to put
your family in a safe place,
before we capture Berdugo.
But, Dad, what if
he already has an idea?
And if he suspects anything,
he won't leave his family.
He'll guard them.
That's why we need
to get ahead of him.
That can only happen...
if Yvette knows what's going on.
She has more leverage.
She can help us.
[SOBBING]
[REBECCA GROANING IN VIDEO]
Andrew...
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
This isn't true, Andrew,
this isn't true.
I'm sorry, Yvette,
but we don't have time.
We need to act now.
I know it's painful, but...
we can't let anyone else
in our family get hurt.
Yvette, we need to be strong,
okay?
For mommy.
For your kids.
Please, Yvette,
don't say mention anything
to Tomas about this.
He must not get any hint
that we know.
How can I do that?
I can't.
I can't, Andrew.
Yvette, you have to, please.
He's not the same person
we thought he was.
Yvette, he must not find out
that we already know everything.
Otherwise, even Harris,
the kids could get
dragged into this.
Yvette, I'm not trying
to scare you,
but we need to prepare
for the worst.
[INQUISITIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
And this is how
we protect our family.
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
Yes.
All right, Andrew.
Tell me...
what I need to do.
[INQUISITIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
[REVVING]
[INQUISITIVE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
[STIRRING MUSIC CONTINUES]
Hon, we're here.
I was just thinking
if I forgot something.
Let's go, kids.
[PHONE CHIMES]
[PHONE KEYS CLICKING]
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Who are you texting?
It's Andrew.
I'm just texting him.
I asked him to come here
so he can join us.
I missed you!
[SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING]
Sir, what if Tomas already knows
that we know he's Berdugo?
What do you mean?
He was tipped off
before we entered?
Isn't that possible, Sir?
We already caught Salazar
before he could tip him off.
He has no eyes on us anymore.
So, let's just focus
on how we'll get the Dizons out.
- Yvette!
- How are you, Mom?
Okay, I'm fine.
Mommy, are you taking
your medicine?
Of course.
Is mommy a good girl, Nanny?
Wow! Good girl.
Oh, don't you want to swim?
She's excited to swim, Mom.
Oh, it's clean!
They cleaned the pool!
It's waiting for you!
See?
It's so exciting.
[INQUISITIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
Listen up!
Secure the perimeter.
No one goes in or out.
Major, Yvette told me
there are many armed guards.
Oh, take note!
Andrew...
you will go in first.
Bring your car.
Secure your family.
Prioritize the kids.
Joey, you'll meet them.
Bring them here.
- Okay?
- Yes, Dad.
Jin Ho, you are coming with me.
You'll identify
if Tomas is indeed Berdugo.
Copy, Sir.
We'll move in two minutes!
Sir, comms check.
Check.
- Check.
Joey, stay in the van.
Don't get out
until the Dizons arrive.
All right.
Be careful, Dad.
Thank you.
Boys, positions!
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
[ENGINE STARTS]
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC CONTINUES]
So, kids, after you swim,
go out to grandmother's garden,
okay?
You can spend time with her.
Grandmother can play with us?
But didn't you say you don't
want her going outside, Mommy?
You said it's not safe for her
to be seen by other people.
You could, just for today.
It's okay.
Right, Mom?
Well, whatever you say.
Isn't it hot outside?
It'll just be for a while, Hon.
It's good for mommy, too...
so she can breathe fresh air.
Ma'am...
your basket is ready.
It's with the guard.
Why?
Because you always go straight
there when you come here.
Oh, yes. Maybe next time.
I want to spend time with them.
Right?
Okay.
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
I'm sorry. Oh, sorry.
Mom, you keep dropping it!
[STIRRING MUSIC CONTINUES]
[CAR HONKING]
Why are there no guards here?
[UNEASY MUSIC PLAYING]
[UNEASY MUSIC CONTINUES]
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[PHONE RINGING]
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
I'm sorry, the subscriber...
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[KNOCKING]
Yvette! Yvette!
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Andrew, why?
Major, the house is locked.
It looks like no one's inside.
No one's answering.
We have to check now.
Wait, Major.
I'll take a look around first,
okay?
Copy.
- Miss...
- Sir Andrew!
What happened?
Sir...
Where are Yvette and the others?
They're inside,
but Sir Tomas has a gun.
He won't let them out.
Major, Yvette and the others
are inside.
Tomas won't let them out.
He has a gun.
Don't go in.
Wait for us.
Come here.
Let's move!
[INQUISITIVE MUSIC CONTINUES]
What's the situation inside?
Sir...
Sir Tomas is armed.
I'm here now.
I'm with Elai.
How are you all there?
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
I'm just waiting for Andrew
to get his family out.
[MOUTHS "COVER"]
[GUN FIRING]
[BULLET PLINKS]
Ma'am, don't go out, okay?
Stay here.
Joey, what's that?
Is there a shootout?
[GUN FIRING]
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
Dad...
[UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING]
I'm here at Berdugo's
rest house.
I'll try to get them out.
I just need help.
This is good,
the connection stable.
Andrew said we're
about to start.
I need a vehicle with two
fully loaded long arms.
If anyone disobeys,
someone will die here.
How long will you hide
behind your hostages?
Is that the Berdugo
everyone fears?
How dare you betray me?
Did you think
I wouldn't sense it?
It's time we execute plan B.
I have an idea.
I'll only talk to you.
If I hear even
the slightest noise,
somebody will die.